- Where is it?
- May I ask what you're looking for?
- You know what I'm looking for. Where is it?
- Goddammit. That's the last one, okay?
Just take it easy on that shit.
That's enough. Put it back.
Can you do me a favor?
Can you save some for the flight?
- Whatever, pussy.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Call me a pussy again, see what happens.
Pussy.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- I don't wanna listen to it anymore.
It doesn't even matter. We're gonna
be drinkin' 40's on an island soon.
Yeah.
- What?
- Pull over.
Come on, man! Don't fuckin' puke in my car!
Jesus Christ!
Are you okay?
Get it all out.
I told you to take it easy.
Fuckin' lightweight.
- You good?
- Never better, baby.
No more stops.
- Fuck.
- Oh, shit.
No... you're making...
you're making it worse. Stop!
Shut up for one second, please.
Nick, stop!
You really are a fuckin' train wreck.
You're the one that decided
to pull into the sand.
Can we, like... wedge a piece
of wood underneath it?
Where do you see a piece of wood
anywhere? Look around. Fuck.
- How far is it to the airfield?
- Thirty miles at least.
Can we walk?
I doubt AAA is gonna be available.
How about you shut the hell up
so I can make this call to Jimmy?
- AAA. Very funny.
- Asshole.
- Hey, man.
- Hey, hey, hey. Jimmy.
- Dog, I got a real problem, man.
- Hello...
You got... hey!
Jimmy, can you hear me? It's Nick.
I can't hear you.
Can you hear me, man?
Jesus Christ.
Nick!
- Nick!
- You don't see me tryin' to do somethin'?
Look.
Who the hell's that?
No, no, no, no, no.
What?
Who is that?
Fuck you. What the fuck?
I got something for you.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What does it look like I'm doing?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Come on! Come on!
- Shoot him in the head!
- I'm trying!
- Just shoot him!
- I need you to shut up for one second!
Okay. Okay. You got it.
Oh, my God!
That's right! Down for the count, bitch!
- Punk bitch! Punk bitch!
- Yeah, you did!
Baby.
They're not as bad as they
make 'em sound on the news.
- No.
- If that motherfucker ain't dead...
- ...he dead now.
- Yeah.
- Are you serious, bro?
- Shoot him in the head.
Shoot him in the head!
Fuck.
- You wanna fuck with me?
- Nick. Nick, it's empty. Nick, it's empty!
Nick, come on, let's go!
Oh, my God, it's gonna break the glass!
Do you think it can break it?
Oh, my God. Jesus, look at it.
Where's the phone?
I dropped it. I dropped it.
- Great. Nick, what're we gonna do now?
- Just wait! Okay?
Give it five minutes.
He's bound to lose interest eventually.
Right?
So we'll just wait, huh?
- Great fuckin' plan.
- Maybe if you learned...
...to handle your shit like an adult,
you would've paid your own phone bill.
Then I could've called Jimmy.
He might be here picking us up right now.
Don't give me that shit.
You're the one who dropped your phone.
Shut the fuck up.
Just shut the fuck up, alright?
Yeah, big bad gangster here, you couldn't
even shoot it from ten feet away.
I swear to God, Molly, if you keep talking...
- What're you gonna do?
- You're really pushing it.
Do it. You fuckin' loser.
Where'd it go?
Turn the high beams on.
Do you see it?
It's too dark.
- Get that flashlight out of my bag.
- Okay.
- Got it. Yep.
- You sure?
I'm sorry.
I think he's gone.
What do you wanna do?
- I gotta get the phone.
- Are you crazy?
What choice do I have?
We've been here the entire time.
There hasn't been a car, a person, nothing.
At least if I get the phone maybe I can
get a hold of Jimmy. He can pick us up.
Okay.
Hey.
- We have to do this.
- Okay, fine.
Okay.
You with me?
Alright.
Shit.
God, it's freezing.
Do you see it?
Oh, my God.
- Nick, I found it!
- Do you got any service?
Molly!
Oh, my God.
Oh, yes. Oh, my gosh. Yes.
- Hello?
- Hey, Jimmy. It's Molly.
Hold on a second. Shut up!
Who?
Molly. Nick's girlfriend.
Yeah. Where's Nick at?
He's... he's just takin' a piss.
Yeah, he just told me to
give you a call, actually.
Tell me that you haven't left yet.
No, no. We haven't left yet, okay?
We're still... we're on the road.
We're gonna cut across the 95
to shoot the shit in the sand.
We're not gonna be there
until like midday tomorrow.
You guys alright? I thought I heard
Nick say there was a problem last night.
No, no problem. No, we're just...
you know, running a bit behind, too.
We probably won't be there
until, like... tomorrow night?
- Maybe the next morning?
- What?
Car trouble, okay? Just... wait for us.
Yeah, okay. Whatever.
You better get here fast, okay, sugar tits?
We'll be there, okay? Just please, wait.
- Tell Nick no promises...
- Jimmy?
Hello?
Shit!
Desert it is.
One foot after another.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, thank God.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Can you smell me or something?
Fuck off!
Maybe you're like a dog.
Do you want it? Okay.
Go fetch! Go fetch!
Get the stick, stupid!
Listen, okay? Get the stick. Fetch. Fetch!
Go get it!
Fuck you!
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, you like that.
Oh, so good.
You wanna taste me? Oh, yeah.
You want some of that?
Oh, that's good, isn't it?
Yeah. That smells so good.
You want my blood? Go fetch!
Shit!
Really?
Too slow, old balls!
I don't really mind
walking through the desert.
You know, it's good cardio.
I gotta get that beach body
ready for Mexico, right?
You're never gonna catch me, man.
You're never gonna catch me.
Leave me the fucking hell alone!
Sucker!
For Christ's sake.
Great.
Come on!
Motherfucker!
Leave me alone!
You're driving me crazy!
You're a fucking stalker, you know that?
I have to kill you.
Do you ever stop making those stupid noises?
Close your mouth or something!
I bet you were a real
ladies man before this, huh?
Obviously, you enjoy the chase.
You're just like every guy
that I've ever met at a bar.
Girl says "no",
guy can't take a fucking hint.
You're all fucking gross.
And you think that suit impresses me?
You look like a used car salesman,
fuckin' douchebag.
Your hair looks stupid, too.
And you smell like shit!
God, you were probably, like,
a fucking idiot when you were alive.
I bet your whole family was retarded.
Inbred, misogynistic fuck-ass fucker!
Small dick.
You know what?
I'm gonna name you.
From now on you'll be known as Small Dick.
Smalls for short.
Come on, Smalls...
...why you goin' so slow?
Don't you want this? You want it?
Yeah? Come on, Smalls.
Yeah, you do.
I guess you have one good quality.
At least you don't talk back.
You are one persistent
son of a bitch, Smalls.
I'll give you that much.
Oh, man, Smalls, you should try some of this.
You want some?
You want a piece? There you go.
Eat that.
How much further do you think it is?
I checked the map a while ago,
but I don't wanna check it again until later.
The battery's gonna die.
It's at least another 15 miles.
But... you know, what's great about coke
is that I don't even need to eat anything.
I think I can probably walk
through the night, to be honest.
No, no, no! Look what you did!
Oh, my God, no!
No!
Such a dick move!
Who are you to judge?
Nick, buddy, you're one lucky son of a bitch.
Listen, we blew the engine out
on the twin last night, okay?
But it's okay 'cause
we're gonna swap it out today...
...and we should have it ready
to go by tomorrow morning.
So you and that dumb broad
better be here by then, okay?
Or we're leaving without you, alright?
I'm fuckin' serious. See ya.
Dumb broad.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Nick...
...the guy that you...
Jesus, that's fucked up.
Honestly...
...I'm not even mad at you over it, really.
He didn't have a lot of redeeming qualities.
I think he had daddy issues.
The truth is, I was just using him
to get out of the city.
I mean, as soon as we got to Mexico
I would have dumped his ass.
Not that it matters.
He was fucking plenty of other girls.
You all are.
Yeah, yeah. Fuck you, too.
I'm so goddamn thirsty.
One more day.
I could maybe even make it there by tonight.
I'm not quitting.
I know you think I will but I'm not.
I am not quitting. You hear that,
Smalls? I'm not quitting!
Help!
Hey!
Hey, are you alright?
Ted, get some water.
Hey!
Hello?
Are you alright?
- Are you hurt?
- No.
Hey, easy. Easy.
- What're you doing way out here?
- Hey.
It's a... a long story.
I've just... been walking.
To where? You're 40 miles away from anything.
An airfield.
Well, you're damn lucky we found you.
It's nearly 100 degrees out here.
- Yeah.
- Right?
Come on, let's get you to the truck.
You can rest there.
Come on, okay? I'll help you up.
It's okay. Yeah, slowly.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
Almost there.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Let me get the A/C.
You feel that?
Yes, I do.
- Oh, God.
- Sorry, I'm Ted.
- Oh, hey. Molly.
- Jason.
Hey.
Shit. Fuck. I... I left
my bag back there, it's...
Hey, no, no, no. Hey, it's okay.
It's okay, we'll get it.
You just... just rest. It's okay.
Okay.
- Over here?
- Yeah, I think so.
I lost it in the... sandstorm.
Shit.
God.
Let's get you to the truck.
Found it!
No, you keep the front.
Sorry, it was buried really deep.
Thanks.
Hey, so what was that about... an airfield?
You know, honestly,
I think that they've left.
Yeah, well... where is it?
Maybe they have some extra planes.
I've flown a few times before.
I don't know.
I mean...
...maybe. It... it's a small airfield.
- Only a few planes.
- It's still worth checking out.
- Yeah.
- You know what, guys...
...I really appreciate all the help, but...
...I think I should probably
just get going on my own now.
Wait a minute. We...
I mean, we can't just leave you out here
alone. You could die of heat stroke.
I think I'll be okay.
But...
...thanks again for everything.
Okay, what the hell? Unlock the fucking door.
Unlock the door!
Get her, man! Go around and get her!
Grab her!
Hold her!
Get out.
- The airfield, where is it?
- Get her up!
Alright, I got her.
Alright, tell us where it is...
...or I'll cut you real deep. You understand?
Just like that dumb nigger and his son.
Okay, it's called Boulder's Airfield,
it's like, six miles north of here, okay?
That's a good little girl.
- Please, just let me go.
- Oh, yeah. No, no.
The pen. God, those are real, aren't they?
- Don't touch me! Don't fuckin' touch me!
- Oh, yeah.
- Get your fucking hands off me!
- Get her in the truck, now!
- Don't you fucking... no!
- Get in the truck.
- Now.
- No!
Fucker! Get your fucking hands
off me. Motherfucker!
No one's gonna hear you
scream out here, okay, bitch?
- Come on, Ted, let's just go!
- You still don't get it!
Everything has changed,
we can do whatever we want.
We can take whatever we want.
- Now help me get her pants off.
- No! No! No!
I'm gonna fuck you so fucking hard.
- Oh, shit, she's bleeding.
- I don't give a fuck!
- Now get in there and hold her still!
- No!
Get up there and hold her still!
- Hold her fucking hands!
- No!
- Please, don't!
- Oh, yeah.
Hurry up! I'm next!
She fuckin' likes it!
We're gonna have to keep you
around for a little bit.
Fuck.
Alright.
Keep going.
Mind passing me
one of those waters back there?
I'm fine.
I don't wanna talk about it.
It happened.
I need to just move on.
Please, just stop!
I just said I don't wanna
talk about it, okay?
Bad shit happens.
Bad shit happens to good people.
I'm a good person.
You just deal with it and you move on.
One foot after another.
Yeah...
...you're right about that.
It's been a real... shit day.
Make it week. It's been a real shit week.
You got kids?
I wonder where they are right now.
I'm sure they're fine.
They probably miss you.
My older sister,
she always wanted to be a mom.
She... she just couldn't have kids.
Her uterus, it's, like, tilted or whatever.
She was so happy to take Chase.
Chase.
That's his name. He's four.
No, five.
She's a way better mom to him
than I ever could be.
I mean, I'm not cut out for that shit.
Look at me.
I mean, I can't take care of him.
I can't even take care of myself.
Ali and Blake, they're...
...they're responsible.
Yeah, they would have gotten
out of the city for sure.
I'm sure they're fine.
Yeah, they're definitely fine.
God, you're a mess, Smalls.
This is ridiculous.
Why am I even talking to you?
You're a fucking walking corpse.
I'm gonna leave you now, okay?
You're... you're starting to slow me down.
Don't look at me like that.
You're gonna be fine.
Someone will come for you eventually, or...
...I don't know. You'll find one
of your own or something, okay?
What do you want me to do?
You can't come with me!
You're just this stupid fucking animal!
You don't even understand me!
Do you?
I'm leaving.
If I take that tire off of you,
do you promise to be good?
Hey! Stay! Stay! Smalls!
Stay!
You ever play that game Telephone?
It's a kid's game.
You take a can...
...and...
...you attach it
to another one with a string...
...and then you pretend it's a phone
and you can hear each other.
Kids love it.
Chase loved it.
We made them together.
This can's my side.
See?
He had been living with my sister
for a while by then.
Last time I saw him...
...I took my can home with me.
I told him that...
...he'd be able to hear me...
...whenever he wanted to.
All he had to do was listen.
I don't even have a picture of him.
All I have is this stupid tin can.
I wanna be at the airfield before noon
so I need you to hustle.
I'm fuckin' done with this sand.
We're almost there.
Come on, Smalls.
It's this way.
Shit! Smalls, we gotta hide you.
Oh, my God. Smalls, come on!
Come on, Smalls, this way! Go!
Smalls! Come here!
There's nothing out here, man.
Convoy thought they seen something.
Let's just check it out.
Come here, Smalls.
I need you to be quiet, okay?
Please be really quiet.
It's hot out.
It's not as hot as that sister of yours.
If you even dream about my sister,
you better wake up and apologize.
Smalls... stay.
Hey, hey, hey. I thought I seen something.
Just relax, huh?
- That over there?
- I don't know.
Just chill, chill.
- Hey!
- Stop right there!
Don't... don't shoot, okay?
It's okay. Please don't shoot.
Ma'am, have you been in contact
with any of the infected?
No, my... my car, it got stuck...
...and I'm just heading to the airfield,
it's just right down the road.
What were you doing back there?
I was using the little girl's room.
What's it look like?
It's not safe out here, ma'am.
You can ride with us.
No, I'm good. I'm good, actually.
My husband's meeting me up there.
- Your husband?
- Yeah.
I'm sure you guys have
more important things to do.
Honestly, I'm good.
Alright.
- You be careful.
- Thanks.
Let's go.
- Stay! Stay! Stay!
- Infected, 12 o'clock!
Jesus Christ, lady!
What the hell's wrong with you?
Please don't shoot! Please don't shoot!
He's not gonna hurt anyone, he's with me!
Please! Just... no one needs to know!
I guess that's the husband.
You know what?
You two... you two have fun.
- Let's get the fuck out of here.
- Come on, Serge!
Get back to the Humvee,
come on, right now. Let's go!
- This is bullshit!
- Let's go right now, that's an order!
- Let's go.
- You're lucky.
Crazy bitch.
Smalls!
I told you to stay!
Why didn't you listen to me?
You could have been killed!
Come on, let's go.
Have a nice day, ma'am!
- You fuckers!
- Good shot.
Okay, Smalls, it's okay. Come on, get up.
Don't be a baby. Let's go, come on.
You've been shot before. Let's do this.
Do not be a baby. Let's go, Smalls.
You got this. Let's go. Let's go!
You bit me!
What the fuck, Smalls?
Oh, my God. Do you...
do you realize what you just did?
Do you?
Oh, my God!
Okay.
Look what you made me do! I'll be lucky
if I don't fucking bleed to death out here!
How could you fucking do this to me?
I should just leave you here to die!
Come on. Come on, Smalls. Get up.
Come on, let's go.
Come on. Come on. You got it, Smalls.
What do you want me to do?
I can't carry you!
Oh, Smalls!
Oh, my God, I can see it!
The airfield!
Jesus, Smalls.
Come on, we're almost there.
Come on, Smalls.
Come on. It's not time for a rest yet.
We're almost there, Smalls, let's go!
Let's go!
Please, Smalls!
Don't worry, I'm not gonna
leave you here like this.
Thank you.
Hello?
Jimmy?
Stop shooting!
Yo, Molly!
Is that you?
Yes, it's fucking me!
Jesus Christ! You scared the shit out of me!
Where's Nick at?
Fuck!
Jimmy's gonna hit that first.
It's 14 miles off the coast.
All they got there
is two villages and that's it.
And even if this has spread...
...it doesn't matter.
I got the full firepower.
The way I figure it, I go in there,
hard, full fuckin' force.
Make it my own.
Jimmy's gonna be El presidente.
We had our own problems, too.
Tommy drives up in that convertible...
...that was a poor choice of vehicle.
Dumb fuck gets bit, doesn't tell anybody.
Infects four of my guys.
I had to lock him up in there.
And this bitch, had a hell of a time
getting it off the ground.
Every time I go to start it, it blows
a gasket. But I think we got it handled.
We good, Robbie?
Hey, Robbie, we good?
- Robbie?
- What?
The fucking plane! Are we good?
Yeah, we'll know in a second, boss.
Guy's been doing speed for two days.
He's a fucking machine.
Is it Shirley? No, it's fuckin' Molly.
It's Molly, right?
Fuck, yeah!
Fuck, it's about time! Grab your shit.
Viva la Mexico!
Come on, Ali. Come on, pick up.
Hi, you've reached Ali and Blake.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Fuck.
- Come on, Ali.
- Hi, you've reached Ali and Blake.
- Please leave a message...
- Fuck!
Hi, you've reached Ali and Blake.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Hello?
Chase!
- Chase, is that you?
- Yeah, who is this?
- It's your mom.
- Ali?
No, Chase, it's... it's your...
your other mom.
Molly.
- Where are you?
- In my bedroom.
You're still at the house?
- Put Ali on.
- I don't know where she is.
She said to lock the door
and hide under the bed.
What? How long have you been hiding for?
- A long time.
- How long, chase?
I don't know.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're so brave. You know that?
Just don't leave from your hiding place.
Don't leave from under your bed
no matter what, okay?
Okay.
I will come for you.
It's...
- I'm pretty far away.
- How long will it take you?
I... I'm not sure. Hopefully not too long.
Why can't you come now?
I'm sorry, Chase,
you're just gonna have to trust me.
You said that before. Why can't you come now?
I'm sorry, Chase,
you're just gonna have to trust me.
Listen, I know that I haven't been around
a lot lately but I'm coming back, okay?
Just hurry, I'm scared.
Okay, listen. I'm leaving right now.
I'll be there soon. I love you.
I'm coming. I promise.
Keys.
No key.
Where's the keys.
Keys, keys.
Come on.
Shit.
Okay.
Fuck you!
Chase?
Chase! Chase!
Chase!
Oh, my God.
Chase.
It's okay, sweetie.
It's me.
It's your mom.
Mommy?
I'm here now.
I made it.
Let's get you out of here.
Give me your hand.
I'm so sorry.
Why did you leave me?
I missed you so much.
I'm so sorry that I left.
I love you.
Okay. Okay.
We gotta go.
I got you.
Mom?
Yeah?
Are you gonna take care of me now?
Yes.
Of course.
Oh, my God. Okay.
No matter what happens, you stay behind me.